mlslistings.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy | MLSListings

MLSLISTINGS INC.

## Privacy

### Privacy Policy, effective as of December 6, 2019.

MLSListings Inc. (“MLSListings”) operates a multiple listing service. As part of the services offered to our participants and subscribers, we have created and maintain this public website.

The privacy of your personal information is very important to us. We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of what information is collected, used, maintained, protected, and disclosed. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MLSListings does not own or control, or to people whom MLSListings does not employ or manage.

MLSListings collects personal information only as allowed by law. We limit the collection of personal information to what is relevant and necessary to accomplish a lawful purpose. We do not sell, share or rent this information other than as disclosed in this policy.

If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Web sites and the related services offered by MLSListings (collectively, the “Site”). By accessing or using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to this Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Information Collection and Use**

The types of information we collect depend on your level of engagement with our Site. The higher the level, the more information we need to provide our services. We collect several types of information from and about users of our Site, including information by which you may be personally identified, such as first and last name, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other information the Site collects that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under an applicable law/any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.

The information we collect on or through our Site may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Site.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Site and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Site.
  * Your search queries on the Site.

Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have consented to these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of MLSListings, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Correcting, Updating, and Deleting Your Information**

To correct, amend or delete your personal information, you can log into the Site and visit your account profile page. You may also send us an email at [support@MLSListings.com](mailto:support@MLSListings.com) to request access to or correct any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

You may request your personal information to be deleted by contacting us at [support@MLSListings.com](mailto:support@MLSListings.com) and we will respond to your request within 30 business days. Even if you request that we delete your personal information, we may still retain data collected from you in an aggregated and anonymized form. We may also still retain your personal information if necessary to: continue providing you with good or services, detect and resolve issues related to security or functionality, and comply with legal and recordkeeping obligations.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other websites. MLSListings does not endorse any third party websites and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site, and to read the privacy statements of websites that collect personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.

**Cookies**

A cookie is software code stored on a user’s hard drive while on our Site. It is not linked to any personally identifiable information, and once the user closes his or her browser, the cookie terminates. If your browser is set to reject cookies, you may still use our Site; however, you will be limited in some areas. For example, you will not be able to complete a property search because our Site uses cookies to “remember” search criteria while you are on the Site.

Servers for our Site automatically receive and record some information into a log. For this Site this includes identifying your browser, this Site cookie information, IP address and the pages you request. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, and gather broad demographic information for use in improving Site performance. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Do Not Track**

Currently, various browsers — including Microsoft Edge, Google Chrome, Firefox, and Safari — offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that relies on a technology known as a DNT header, which sends a signal to Web sites’ visited by the user about the user's browser DNT preference setting. MLSListings does not currently commit to responding to browsers' DNT signals with respect to the Site, in part, because no common industry standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators, including no consistent standard of interpreting user intent. MLSListings takes privacy and meaningful choice seriously and will make efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard.

**Use of Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, which allows us to understand the overall use of our Site and services. Google Analytics collects information such as how frequently users visit the Site, how many users visit the Site, and what pages they visit. Google Analytics provides us this data in aggregated form.

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics is dictated by the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](https://marketingplatform.google.com/about/analytics/terms/us/) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You may opt-out of Google Analytics by installing Google’s opt-out browser add-on [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our Site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose requested information. Contact information will be used to notify winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this Site.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

MLSListings reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will mean you accept those changes. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy here and may notify you by email or by means of a notice on our Site.

**_Security Statement_**

_MLSListings maintains reasonable and appropriate measures to protect the personal information obtained through the Site and in connection with our services from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.  
_

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@MLSListings.com](mailto:support@MLSListings.com) or call Customer Support at (866) 734-5787.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request."

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: write to us at [support@MLSListings.com](mailto:support@MLSListings.com) or call Customer Support at (866) 734-5787.
